JOHN JANG

Product Designer

iscolbe9675@gmail.com

My portfolio

SUMMARY

A Product Designer, graduated from York University in Toronto, Ontario, Canada, with over a year of professional experience in crafting user experience that suits the branding and another year of experience in web development. I am proficient in designing products from scratch till the launch, while considering the development perspective such as the User Interface development, CI/CD pipeline, deployment, etc. My strengths include strategic designing, initiating projects, and leading communications with internal and external teams. By nature, I am analytical, perceptive, and enjoy problem-solving. Outside of work, I am a runner, dancer, and a potential traveler.

EXPERIENCE

Product Designer

OperateEase

08 / 2024 ~ Present | Remote, Toronto

- Developed a comprehensive design system to standardize UI components and hosted UX Design workshops to align with stakeholders and gather insights from users
- Led the design of an inventory management system, optimizing room occupancy and supply management, increasing efficiency by 60%
- Collaborated closely with engineering teams to ensure design feasibility and maintain a high standard of quality across all features

Product Designer Intern

The Sakhi

06 / 2024 ~ 10 / 2024 | Remote, Toronto

 Conducted regular design critique sessions with Shopify developers to refine features and functionality based on feedback

UX Designer

TuGo Travel

03 / 2024 \sim 05 / 2024 | Remote, Toronto

UX/UI Design Apprentice TeleVU Innovation

06 / 2022 ~ 08 / 2022 | Remote, Toronto

English as a Second Language Instructor Miller English Academy

02 / 2021 \sim 12 / 2021 | Remote, Toronto

English as a Second Language Instructor SLP Korea

02 / 2020 ~ 01 / 2021 | Remote, Toronto

VOLUNTEER

Web Development Apprentice Tech Fleet Professional Association

08 / 2023 ~ 09 / 2024 | Remote, Toronto

UX/UI Design Apprentice

Tech Fleet Professional Association

04 / 2023 ~ 07 / 2023 | Remote, Toronto

EDUCATION

UX Design

York University

North York, Ontario

Web Development Bootcamp Pream Coding Academy

Remote, Toronto

Psychology & Neuroscience University of New Brunswick

Fredericton, NB

TOOLS & SKILLS

Figma, Figjam, Miro, Wireframing, Sketching, Typography, Prototyping, Mock-ups, A/B Testing, Usability Testing Waterfall, User-Interface Design, User Research HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, TypeScript, Next.js, React, Vite, MongoDB, Express.js, Axios

OTHER LINKS

<u>LinkedIn - John Janq</u>
<u>My Web Development Portfolio</u>
My Github Profile